<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jupyter on Mohit Sharma</title>
    <link>https://sharmamohit.com/tags/jupyter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jupyter on Mohit Sharma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Mohit Sharma</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 00:59:02 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/jupyter/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>jupyter notebooks in blog</title>
      <link>https://sharmamohit.com/post/jupyter-notebooks-in-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 00:59:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sharmamohit.com/post/jupyter-notebooks-in-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I love Jupyter notebooks! They are great for experimenting and playing around with the ideas. I always liked the idea of using a single web based application for writing code snippets, visualizations, creating presentations and even blogging! &lt;br/&gt;
There are great static website generators out there but most of them use restructured text or markdown to convert to html pages. 
&lt;br&gt;
Developers of jupyter notebooks have now embedded the nbconvert tool for converting notebooks (&lt;code&gt;ipynb&lt;/code&gt;) to Markdown (&lt;code&gt;md&lt;/code&gt;) or ReStructuredText (&lt;code&gt;reST&lt;/code&gt;) and even standalone &lt;code&gt;html&lt;/code&gt; with all the css stylings. Regardless of whether you use blogging engines like &lt;a href=&#34;https://wordpress.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Wordpress&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or static website generators like &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Hugo&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the issue of formatting the notebook so that they play well with your website has always persisted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;using-jupyter-notebooks-in-your-blog&#34;&gt;Using Jupyter notebooks in your blog&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always had two options:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Convert Notebooks to Markdown&lt;br/&gt;
Use Jupyter notebook&amp;rsquo;s built-in command to convert to markdown and then spend 20 more minutes correcting formatting, image&amp;rsquo;s that are embedded, code blocks, etc. I would then convert to html using &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Hugo&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.getpelican.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Pelican&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; website generator (based on what I am using for my website) and then publish it online.  Problem with this method? Formatiing, Code samples, Code coloring, everything lost!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Convert Notebooks directly to html&lt;br/&gt;
Use Jupyter notebook&amp;rsquo;s built-in command to convert to html and use it in my blog. Issues with this? Horrible CSS! Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong. The html output from Jupyter&amp;rsquo;s nbconvert was meant to provide a decent layout and styling for a standalone professional html file.. and it does that well. However if you are like me, you have some global layout style that you want your notebook in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;available-tools&#34;&gt;Available Tools&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have used:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/danielfrg/pelican-ipynb&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;pelican-ipynb&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; plugin for blogging using ipython (or Jupyter) notebook. However I had a hard time setting it up. Plus there were some incompatibilities with the themes that I was using. It is a good tool and you can check it out here: (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/danielfrg/pelican-ipynb&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://github.com/danielfrg/pelican-ipynb&lt;/a&gt;) but I wanted something that would.. Just.. Work!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://getnikola.com/blog/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Nikola&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; static website generator just like &lt;code&gt;Hugo&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;Pelican&lt;/code&gt;. It has an added advantage that it supports blogging via notebooks right out of the box. Sweet! but it is really targeted at making a blog first that means main page always seems to be the blogroll. Whereas I wanted a single page academic website having my intro on top and publications and then posts with some kind of blogroll in there. Anyways it really felt targeted towards a blog site or a site with lots of posts. Moreover it uses &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.makotemplates.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Mako&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; templating engine whereas I was more familiar with &lt;a href=&#34;http://jinja.pocoo.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;jinja&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://golang.org/pkg/html/template/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Go&lt;/code&gt; template library&lt;/a&gt;. Anyways in the end, I decided to stick with either &lt;code&gt;Pelican&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;Hugo&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have spent enough hours trying to google and reading forums to realize that there is no one tool to solve it all. In the end I decided to do this manually. I opened chrome developer tools and started analyzing the generated html page. &lt;br/&gt;
Stripping away as much css styling as possible, I was finally able to create a barebones version of css styling that can be used with the exported html page  (from notebook using nbconvert).
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now whenever you want to embed your notebook in your blog, you can simply:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Convert the jupyter notebook to basic html file:
&lt;code&gt;
jupyter nbconvert --to html --template basic *source_file.ipynb* *target_file.html*
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Download the &lt;a href=&#34;http://sharmamohit.com/css/jupyter.css&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;jupyter.css&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; file and place it in your css folder of your website.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now simply modify your base index html file or whatever it is that contains the boiler plate/ placeholder for your website by adding a css tag linking to this file.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
